NLRB 50th Anniversary Conference Tapes and Transcripts 5740 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB 50th Anniversary Conference Tapes and Transcripts
1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
5740 OH
2.39 cubic feet
2.4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The NLRB's 50h Anniversary Conference was held athe the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations ( the ILR School) in October, 1984
5699384
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 13, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Scope and Contents
The NLRB's 50h Anniversary Conference was held athe the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations ( the ILR School) in October, 1984
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files 5435 OH: NLRB Oral History Project Miscellaneous 5843: NLRB Miscellaneous Tapes and Transcripts 5847: Paul M. Herzog Papers 6058 OH: Kheel Center Collection of Oral Histories
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; United States. National Labor Relations Board.
5699384
- NLRB Conference Transcript [p.1-80] (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NLRB Conference Transcript [p.81-end] (Box 1, Folder 2)
- McCulloch, F. [died Summer 1996] (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NLRB Conference [carbon copy] (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Farmer Interview [corrected] (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NLRB - Miller [Ed Miller] (Box 1, Folder 6)
- John Farming (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  side I-II
- John Farming (Box 3, Folder 1)
  side III-IV
- John Farming (Box 4, Folder 1)
  side V-VI
- John Farming (Box 5, Folder 1)
  side VII-VIII
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  side IX-X
- Frank McCulloch - 12/7/1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  side XI-XII
- Guy Farmer - 12/5/1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Guy Farmer - 12/5/1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Guy Farmer - 12/5/1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Ed Miller (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Ed Miller (Box 16, Folder 1)
- NLRB - 10/22/1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  tape 2, side I-II
- NLRB - 10/22/1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  tape I - side I-II
- Audio digitized from the collection. (Box 19)